<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<LanguageData>
    <StatReport_SocialPsychicHigh>Psychic sensitivity +/= 200%</StatReport_SocialPsychicHigh>
    <GreaterFoxianBornTitle>{0} born</GreaterFoxianBornTitle>
    <GreaterFoxianBornLoc>{0_nameDef} has born a {1}</GreaterFoxianBornLoc>
    <GeneticPurityErrorLabel>Genetic Purity Error !</GeneticPurityErrorLabel>
    <GeneticPurityErrorDesc>There has been an error when trying to initialize the genetic purity gene. The error is most likely due to a xenotype being removed and still being present in the config file. Please open the mod settings for the Foxian race to reset the values set on xenotype A or B. In the meantime, the erroneous values have been set to only Foxians or greater Foxians until the config for the mod has been opened and the error resolved.</GeneticPurityErrorDesc>
    <CursedSwordBerseker>{0_nameDef} has tried unequipping his weapon. But in doing so, he awoke the ire of the spirit inhabiting his sword, and {0_nameDef}'s mind temporarily broke as a result of the spirit's retaliation.</CursedSwordBerseker>
    <FoxianModName>Foxian Race</FoxianModName>
    <FoxianModSettingsWarning>Changing any values might require a restart or reloading a save !</FoxianModSettingsWarning>
    <FoxianInformation>You can get more information on each setting by hovering your mouse on the label.</FoxianInformation>
    <FoxianInformationDesc>Yes, even this one...</FoxianInformationDesc>
    <HoverForInfo>(Hover for more informations)</HoverForInfo>
    <PsychicManipulationSettings>Psychic Manipulation Threshold</PsychicManipulationSettings>
    <PsychicManipulationSettingsDesc>This number means you gain a bonus social skill point for every x% psychic sensitivity beyond 100%. Each pawn has a basic value of 100% psychic sensitivity (unless they have traits or genes that change the default value).\nBy default, the value of the threshold is 25%, so a pawn with 150% psychic sensitivity will gain 2 bonus social skills points.</PsychicManipulationSettingsDesc>
    <PsychicManipulationSettingSkillsDropDown>Psychic manipulation affects this skill: </PsychicManipulationSettingSkillsDropDown>
    <PsychicManipulationSettingSkillsDropDownDesc>The skill shown in the button will be the one to receive the bonus skill points for the gene.</PsychicManipulationSettingSkillsDropDownDesc>
    <PsychicManipConstruction>Construction</PsychicManipConstruction>
    <PsychicManipPlants>Plants</PsychicManipPlants>
    <PsychicManipIntellectual>Intellectual</PsychicManipIntellectual>
    <PsychicManipMining>Mining</PsychicManipMining>
    <PsychicManipShooting>Shooting</PsychicManipShooting>
    <PsychicManipMelee>Melee</PsychicManipMelee>
    <PsychicManipSocial>Social</PsychicManipSocial>
    <PsychicManipAnimals>Animals</PsychicManipAnimals>
    <PsychicManipCooking>Cooking</PsychicManipCooking>
    <PsychicManipMedicine>Medicine</PsychicManipMedicine>
    <PsychicManipArtistic>Artistic</PsychicManipArtistic>
    <PsychicManipCrafting>Crafting</PsychicManipCrafting>
    <AnimalConnectionSettings>Animal Connection Trigger Threshold</AnimalConnectionSettings>
    <AnimalConnectionSettingsDesc>This threshold represents how much psychic sensitivity a pawn needs to trigger the effect of "Animal Connection". By default, the value is set to 150%. Setting that value to 0% will deactivate the trigger.</AnimalConnectionSettingsDesc>
    <GeneticPurityFoxianTrigger>Should a person be a Foxian to trigger the genetic purity gene ?</GeneticPurityFoxianTrigger>
    <GeneticPurityFoxianTriggerDesc>By default, only a Foxian or a person considered "Foxian enough" can birth an offspring with xenotype A or B. Otherwise, they will transmit all their genes to the offspring. By deactivating this condition, everyone with this gene would be able to birth Xenotype A or B, whetever they are Foxian or not.</GeneticPurityFoxianTriggerDesc>
    <GeneticPuritySettingXenotypeA>Choose xenotype A: </GeneticPuritySettingXenotypeA>
    <GeneticPuritySettingXenotypeADesc>The xenotype shown in the button will be the one used for creating an offspring with xenotype A. By default, xenotype A is set to the Foxian xenotype.</GeneticPuritySettingXenotypeADesc>
    <GeneticPuritySettingXenotypeB>Choose xenotype B: </GeneticPuritySettingXenotypeB>
    <GeneticPuritySettingXenotypeBDesc>The xenotype shown in the button will be the one used for creating an offspring with xenotype B. By default, xenotype B is set to the Greater Foxian xenotype.</GeneticPuritySettingXenotypeBDesc>
    <ResetButton>Default Values</ResetButton>
</LanguageData>