<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

  <XenotypeDef>
    <defName>FL_Foxian</defName>
    <label>Foxian</label>
    <description>Foxians are newly discovered human-fox-like hybrids unique to this specific rimworld. They are more attuned to the psychic world than the average person. They can use their psychic sensitivity as a way to manipulate others into doing what they want, and their attunement to nature allows them to easily understand animals and how to communicate with them. They avoid deserts or any other hot climates in favor of colder ones. They are composed and calm, so they won't fight their peers or succumb to violent breakdowns, and they are loyal to their cause. Despite their strengths, they possess weaknesses such as a weak aptitude in melee, a weak immune system with a high sensitivity to toxic gas, and they are very vulnerable to fire damage due to their tail being easily flammable. Their most unique characteristic is the fact that all the foxians are female and their offspring are always born as another foxian. There is also the rare possibility of the offspring being a greater foxian. Greater foxians are majorly male, but some female variants exist.</description>
    <descriptionShort>Foxians are human-fox-like hybrids. They are attuned to the psychic world and thus can manipulate other persons and understand animals better than others. They are socially composed and calm, so they won't fight their peers or enter violent mental breakdowns. Furthermore, they are weak to fire, high temperature, and toxic damage and have a bad aptitude for melee. Their most unique trait is their genetic purity. All the foxians are female, and their offspring are always born as a female foxian, in some rare cases, they can birth a greater foxian, which can be male.</descriptionShort>
    <iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotype/FL_FoxianXenotypeIcon</iconPath>
    <inheritable>true</inheritable>
    <combatPowerFactor>1.0</combatPowerFactor>
    <genes>
      <li>Beauty_Pretty</li>
      <li>FL_FoxEar</li>
      <li>FL_FoxTail</li>
      <li>FL_LowFertility</li>
      <li>FL_Lustful</li>
      <li>FL_Reserved</li>
      <li>FL_Loyal</li>
      <li>FL_NaturalPsySensitive</li>
      <li>AptitudeStrong_Animals</li>
      <li>MinTemp_SmallDecrease</li>
      <li>MaxTemp_SmallDecrease</li>
      <li>FL_Immaculate</li>
      <li>FL_Female</li>
      <li>FireWeakness</li>
      <li>FL_ToxicVulnerability</li>
      <li>FL_PsychicManipulation</li>
      <li>FL_GeneticPurity</li>
      <li>FL_Composed</li>
      <li>FL_Emotionally_Brittle</li>
      <li>FL_AnimalConnection</li>
    </genes>
  </XenotypeDef>

  <XenotypeDef>
    <defName>FL_Greater_Foxian</defName>
    <label>Greater Foxian</label>
    <description>Greater Foxians are almost similar to their foxian cousins. But instead of using their psychic power to manipulate the minds of other humans or animals, they wield it to enhance their combat abilities. The higher their psychic sensitivity, the more damage they deal with their melee weapons. They can turn their sensitivity into a psychic shield to cushion incoming hits or use it as a form of prescience to dodge them. In the event of something dire happening, they can use their last stand ability, which gathers all their psychic energy as a last desperate measure to fend off their enemies. This is mostly used to protect their wounded comrades from death. They are affected by a weak immunity, but their open wounds close much quicker than their foxian counterpart. Their strength in combat is counterbalanced with their horrible aptitude in shooting and agriculture. They live longer than normal Foxians.</description>
    <descriptionShort>Greater Foxians are almost similar to their foxian cousins. But instead of using their psychic power for social purpose, they wield it to gain the advantage in combat. They are formidable melee warriors that can last long and hit hard as long as their psychic sensitivity is high. They can use an ability in desperate measure to fend off the last enemies in dire circumstances. As a result of their combat prowess, they are terrible at using guns and agricultural works. They live longer than Foxians.</descriptionShort>
    <iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotype/FL_GreaterFoxianXenotypeIcon</iconPath>
    <inheritable>true</inheritable>
    <combatPowerFactor>1.5</combatPowerFactor>
    <genes>
      <li>Beauty_Beautiful</li>
      <li>FL_FoxEar</li>
      <li>FL_NineFoxTail</li>
      <li>FL_LowFertility</li>
      <li>FL_Lustful</li>
      <li>FL_Reserved</li>
      <li>FL_Loyal</li>
      <li>FL_NaturalPsySensitive</li>
      <li>AptitudeStrong_Melee</li>
      <li>AptitudeTerrible_Shooting</li>
      <li>AptitudePoor_Plants</li>
      <li>AptitudePoor_Animals</li>
      <li>MinTemp_SmallDecrease</li>
      <li>MaxTemp_SmallDecrease</li>
      <li>FireWeakness</li>
      <li>FL_SlowAging</li>
      <li>FL_ToxicVulnerability</li>
      <li>Superclotting</li>
      <li>Immunity_Weak</li>
      <li>FL_GeneticPurity</li>
      <li>FL_Composed</li>
      <li>FL_Emotionally_Brittle</li>
      <li>FL_PsychicChanneling</li>
      <li>FL_PsychicProtection</li>
      <li>FL_LastStand</li>
    </genes>
  </XenotypeDef>
</Defs>